

Ahad Sheibani

Front-End Developer

DoB: 1993/9/13 Marital Status: Single Military Service: Served

junior Developer with over 2 years of experience in front-end coding and deployment in a JavaScript environment and developing websites and web applications with react js. 2 years of above experience in working with live applications and troubleshooting exprtiese.

Contact ahad.sh1372@gmail.com (+98)9016360599 www.ahadsheibani.info Jahad avenue alley 56-132, Kerman, Iran Skills web developer javascript, bootstarp react js react and redux context Material-UI html/css Cypress

Tailwind CSS



Education

Bachelor of Urban planning

Branch: planing

Institute/University: Azad university

2012 - 2016



Work Experiences

front-end developer

Company: Cashcool

January 2020 - November 2020

front-end developer

Company: Achange

December 2020 - March 2021

front-end developer

Company: Smart-Bees



Languages

English					
Reading Level	•	_	_		
Writing Level	•				
Speaking Level	•				
Listening Level					



Certificates

HTML, CSS AND JAVASCRIPT FOR WEB DEVELOPERS

Institute: Coursera Date: June 2021

INTRODUCTION TO HTML5



in ahad-sheibani

y ahad47281666

ahadsh72

ahad-sheibani

Institute: Coursera Date: March 2021

React + Redux course

Institute: Solo Learn
Date: June 2021



Projects

Web Application

For: CashCool team

Link: club.cashcool.cash

web application

For: Smart-bees
Link: smartbees.app

Instagram clone

For: open source project

Link: github.com/ahad-sheibani/InstagramClone

Portfolio Website

For: open source project

Link: github.com/ahad-sheibani/Portfolio

Ö

Honors

sixth place Sanati Sharif MPM Marathon

Date: October 2020